Hey guys, watch this!
I'm better! See? I can do three!
- Cool!
- Wow!
- Amazing!
- Lame!
I'm spinning seven!
You think anyone cares?!
How many can you do, Needy?
[SLOWED DOWN]
Needy?
[EVEN MORE SLOWED DOWN]
Nee-
[SLOW SPEED PROGRESSING TO NORMAL SPEED]
Don't call me Needy!
[INTRO PLAYS]
Subtitles: TAFFYMARZI
It's time for Cake at Stake
for the team that lost last time.
Even though they were in first place for a while,
Coiny's team came in last.
So let's go Coiny, Icy, and Needy.
We got eighteen votes. A record high!
So, yeah. I've got two halves of a cake.
One of you will not get one.
If you don't, you are eliminated.
Needle, you have a win token.
Would you like to use it now?
- Yeah!
- Announcer: Okay.
Where is it?
There we go!
Okay then!
So, Ice Cube, you are at the lowest
with one vote!
Announcer:
LLOSMMORPG voted for you.
He was the only one.
The oddball in the group of normal voters.
There is only one cake half left,
but there are two people.
Awkward silence...
You know what, Coiny?
You haven't spoken once at my Cake at Stakes.
You're just contributing to the silence.
Coiny:
Hey, look here! I'm contributing!
Instead of spending time on what I want to do,
I'm helping out and contributing to something else!
[sing-song] The sound of silence!
- Okay, so-
- Shhh!
We have to contribute to the silence!
- Coiny, you got-
- Shhh!
- The per-
- Out of the final-
- Shhhh!
Grrrr!
Needy.
Now that Coiny is gone, I can talk.
Announcer:
Coiny is at five votes,
and Needy-
is it twelve votes.
Announcer:
Because she used her win token, she's down to six votes;
but that's still the highest, so Needle is out.
Needle: Aw, seriously?
That proves that the number thirteen is unlucky.
Because Needle had slapped exactly thirteen times
before she learned she was eliminated.
Do you think Nonexistent Icy is mad at me?
Needy!
Yeah, I guess it's pretty big, Needy.
Leafy:
Didn't it, Needy?!
What's wrong with calling you Needy, Needy?!
Don't you, Needy?!
I love Needies!
Do you know where she is, Needy?
Coiny, Icy, Needy-
[SLOWED DOWN[
Neee-
So let's go Coiny, Icy, and Needy.
Needy-
...and Needy-
is at twelve votes.
Yeah, but, Needle, why don't you like being called Needy?
Needy-
Why won't it close all the way?
What?! Can't you read?!
The carrying capacity is six!
There are six people in there, but Spongy's kinda big.
Oh well. In that case,
there's no room to eliminate another player.
So, in the next contest-
Which is?!
I'm getting to that right now.
Anyway, in the next contest, this contest's winning team
chooses a contestant from the contest's losing team
to be on their team; so no one gets sent to the TLC.
Yeah!
Eraser:
But what is the contest?!
Okay. Enter that room.
Announcer:
Ha ha. I tricked you! Now you are trapped in this room.
There is no way out.
Oh no!
Does that mean we'll starve to death in here?!
We'll find out after the break.
Want skin that's smooth and soft?!
Then buy our Bubble Transformer!
It'll turn you into a bubble,
and Bubble's skin is super smooth!
None of the people in our
survey said they didn't like it!
Because they popped before we could contact them,
and we don't sell personal Bubble Recovery Centers.
So they died...
Euhhh...
So yeah! Buy now!
Everyone:
AHHHH!
People, calm down!
There is a way out of here.
Liar, liar, pants of blaze!
No, Pence-Pence, it's true.
Only I call her Pence-Pence!
Oh, so now you're a slapper too, aren't you?
Hey guys, look! To pass the time, we can try to finish
these jigsaw puzzles on the floor!
That's exactly what the seventh contest is.
Announcer:
If your team completes your team's jigsaw puzzle,
the doors will detetct it and let you free.
Until then, you're trapped.
Announcer:
The fastest team wins. And go.
This should be easy!
Yeah! Especially because there are only nine pieces!
'Kay, let's get going!
You know, this is really hard because
they're all the same dark brown color!
Something tells me we're doing something wrong!
You worry too much, Pencil.
Gimme that!
Squashy Grapes:
YEEAAH!
There's one more thing I want you to do.
Squashy Grapes:
AHHHHH!
Before I'll let you go, choose someone on
the Squishy Cherries to be on your team.
Okay then, let's see who we can choose from!
Coiny:
There's Eraser, his friend, and
the dumb jerk, and the alliance.
Coiny:
So let's take a vote!
Who do you want, Icy?
Ice Cube:
Pencil!
The rest of you?
Everyone:
FIREY!
Coiny:
And I don't want Firey. I guess Firey won't be the one!
We pick Firey!
But I hate Firey!
Why would you do that?!
Oh no! Now Coiny's on my team?!
Okay, so now the Squashy Grapes
really, really outnumber the Squishy Cherries.
Yeah, it was so funny!
Match:
Eraser just, like, walked up and stepped on a nail!
Hoy hoy! That's so hilar!
But then he, like, shot up in the air,
and he so totally fell on, like, a bed of nails!
Yeah, yeah! Wow!
Eraser:
Hey, Match and Pencil!
You two better not be talking about me!
And why aren't you helping us on the puzzle anyway?
Oh great, now you're bossy!
I was glad when Pin, like, was eliminated,
but now you're like her!
Eraser:
I just wanna finish the puzzle, okay?
Sure...
Huuh... Yeh...
GUYS!
All the pieces are upside down!
The brown goes on the back!
Eraser:
Ohh, no wonder!
So yeah, Cherries, keep working.
Because you're still trapped in this room.
And that means no voting for this episode!
However, episode eight will still come out on August 1st, and there will be voting then!
Hey! I found two pieces that fir together!
- Pencil: Finally!
- Eraser: It's about time!